what the heck is going on everybody
welcome
your very first to ruin I O S the
bellman
with swift now in this is world series
well I'm going to do
is I'm gonna show you guys had a great
are some I West aP's
and that includes the iPad the iPod
Touch
the iPhone any actually you wanna make
well
you are not because this is the greatest
World Series
ever created noun before you started I
want to mention a couple things
for small what is swept I never heard in
this thing called swift before
going to mail your computer programming
model a know what the heck's going on
there
well whenever Apple first allow
developers make
arm like I was axed for the iPhone or
whatever they used a programming
language called objective-c
but now just a few months ago they came
out with the brand new language coats
with
and it's pretty much the future %uh I
was the bellman
so before we get into you know adding
all the buns and stuff on your haps
I'm gonna teach you guys this computer
programming language
and then once we learn basis abet we can
move on to making cool like iPad app for
iPhone app's what everyone knew
so now that is underway
let's go ahead and get started I don't
want to be as you know like a huge a
long intro about the history of it but
you notice a little quick info so the
first thing you need to do when everyone
create Iowa sabes is
you need an Apple ID and if you go to
this website right here
developer dot Apple dot com you probably
already have one
if you're working with Matt this is
where you can pretty much
arm set up all your accounts of so the
first thing you need is an Apple ID
so if you click this pine in Apple ID is
pretty much just so
I don't know like any arm like Google
has you make an account ya whom it has
you make an account
well this is like Apple's account for
their main on overall everything
so of course you just fill in your first
name are your email password typical
stuff right here
I actually already have an Apple ID and
like I said I'm guessing you do too
absence text me ray in the middle my
store /url
much worse go ahead and
read it word is this a is my moon
noon she says dinner at her house
tonight they're having meatballs
so looks like I'll be eating me post
money cool cool are
so now they have an Apple ID again I
didn't want to talk you through that
because like typing your name type in
your last name
movie you know you guys keep hearing
that out but now what we need to do
is we need to create a developer account
now whenever we have a developer account
what we can do this is we can download
all the cool tools
like Xcode and Xcode is pretty
it's just like a really fancy text
editor that you can use to rate your
code
and there's also like the IRS SDK that
we need
in this is pretty much arm in the
software development kit specific to I
was absolutely awful stuff
Taylor to developing like iPhone and
iPad app so those are two things that we
need to get
so let's go ahead and sign in now if you
had to do that
so sign in almost lost their developer
Kunis sign in okay
lonely it but i wanna be come are
Apple Developer the NRA so
definitely read all that I know it look
like I was a remember trust me as I am
original speed reading 11 are so just
agree to this
in OK are your first question what role
best describes you probably aren't like
incredibly good-looking deny
no don't know that one so to say that I
am A R
suffer engineer when he started building
for Apple platforms will say
pick whatever we want now what are you
developing
I'm only been shown you guys had to
develop Iowa saps
anything for mobile handheld devices
so I'm just going to click abstrait
there we can also do with this
these tools is you can just develop like
regular software
for the Mac like I don't know I programs
like Skype in
you know like photo editors whatever you
want so if you wanna
do any that then you can follow whatever
but again this is for a series is just
for
iPhone in Iowa saps so okay
were other platforms to develop forward
Android
in a a merchant when those two little
bit driver
on the side re: now register think
courageous there you are now
able to sign in to the website so hit
continue and check this out